Hi, my name is Ari Rgoode. I am a full
-stack Python developer with HealthKERI,
and my presentation was on KRAM, which is
KERI Request Authentication Mechanism. I
think what I do and see differently is I'm
really engaged with moving the healthcare
industry specifically towards a
repudiable, individually owned mode of
data governance and transmission. So if
KRAM disappeared tomorrow, we would lose a
huge step towards replay attack
protections in the KERI ecosystem.
Previously, everybody had their own
bespoke methods for doing this when
implementing with ShareAPI, and it is very
beneficial for the ecosystem to leave
everybody into the same modality of
protection that is proven and trusted
throughout the different implementers.